[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "sectionTitle": "Animals",
    "code": "animal",
    "group": [
      {
        "quizTitle": "Pets",
        "quiz": [
          {
            "question": "How many pets do you have?",
            "answer": "Couple of Meows"
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you like dogs?",
            "answer": "Let me think ..."
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizTitle": "Giraffe",
        "quiz": [
          {
            "question": "How tall a regular giraffe",
            "answer": "Taller than me :)"
          },
          {
            "question": "Are they fast at running?",
            "answer": "Faster than me :)"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizTitle": "Owl",
        "quiz": [
          {
            "question": "Have you ever seen an owl?",
            "answer": "Yes I have, on YT."
          },
          {
            "question": "Are they predators?",
            "answer": "Definitely"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "sectionTitle": "Music",
    "code": "music",
    "group": [
      {
        "quizTitle": "Pop music",
        "quiz": [
          {
            "question": "Do you like pop music?",
            "answer": "Depends on my mood"
          },
          {
            "question": "What type of music do you usually listen to?",
            "answer": "Classical music"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizTitle": "Sounds",
        "quiz": [
          {
            "question": "What sounds irritates you most?",
            "answer": "any unexpected loud sound"
          },
          {
            "question": "What sound do you like most?",
            "answer": "Silence"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizTitle": "Rock",
        "quiz": [
          {
            "question": "RockNRoll or Heavy metal?",
            "answer": "R&Roll"
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you dance on rock music?",
            "answer": "Oh yeah"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "sectionTitle": "Vehicles",
    "code": "cars",
    "group": [
      {
        "quizTitle": "Favorite car",
        "quiz": [
          {
            "question": "You favorite car?",
            "answer": "SUV"
          },
          {
            "question": "Do you have a car?",
            "answer": "I prefer bikes"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizTitle": "Japan autos",
        "quiz": [
          {
            "question": "Have you ever driven Japanese cars",
            "answer": "I have"
          },
          {
            "question": "Your favorite Japanese car?",
            "answer": "All of them are good."
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizTitle": "Steering wheel",
        "quiz": [
          {
            "question": "Right or left?",
            "answer": "doesn't matter"
          },
          {
            "question": "Automatic or manual?",
            "answer": "Of course Automatic"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "sectionTitle": "Technology",
    "code": "technology",
    "group": [
      {
        "quizTitle": "SmartPhone",
        "quiz": [
          {
            "question": "Smart or Phone?",
            "answer": "Smartphone"
          },
          {
            "question": "techno or logy",
            "answer": "technology"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizTitle": "OS",
        "quiz": [
          {
            "question": "What OS do you prefer to work with?",
            "answer": "Linux Ubuntu"
          },
          {
            "question": "What about macOS?",
            "answer": "Never worked with, but I would love to"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizTitle": "Future",
        "quiz": [
          {
            "question": "Would you like to travel to the future",
            "answer": "I'm scared of thinking about it, but I would definitely"
          },
          {
            "question": "Android or iOS?",
            "answer": "That, which has a good camera"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]
